Audrey Sperry

SOFTWARE & WEB DEVELOPER

SKILLS

Java | Spring Boot | Thymeleaf IntelliJ | Junit | JPA | Hibernate

Node.js | Express | JS | JQuery SQL | Sequelize | Postgresql Mongodb | Mongoose | Jest

RESTful APIs | TDD | GIT | MVC Github DataGrip | Heroku

HTML | CSS | Bootstrap | Flexbox | Responsive Design | Fetch Rqsts

ABOUT

In 2016 a colleague and I set out to design a tool to make it easier for our mission-driven clients to manage the systems that sustain their impact. This incredibly educational, challenging and rewarding experience opened my eyes to the world of software development and I haven't looked back. As a professional software developer I look forward to solving problems and tackling challenges for a company with the same passion, enthusiasm, and sense of humor that I approach the rest of my life with.



audrey.sperry@gmail.com 860.874.2756



<u>audreysperry.com</u> <u>linkedin.com/in/audreysperry</u> github.com/audreysperry

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Web & Software Development Student

The Iron Yard Greenville Summer 2017

The Iron Yard is a 12-week coding bootcamp specializing in highly focused, immersive training centered on language fluency, object-oriented programming, and project-based learning.

Strategy Consultant

Gather Consulting 2015-2017

- Facilitated organization and community-wide collaborative efforts including strategic planning, focus groups and mergers
- Guided community and nonprofit leaders through major decisions using facilitation and collaboration strategies
- Recruited clients, drafted proposals, and secured projects
- Managed the implementation of work to ensure clients' needs were met, and the project completed on time

Active Lifestyles Coordinator

Partners for Active Living 2014-2016

- Spearheaded the development of a new database management system for community bike rental program
- Project managed all aspects of annual professional cycling race, doubled revenue of previous year and surpassed attendance and participation goals
- Revamped marketing and customer service for bicycle sharing system resulting in increased ridership and revenue

EDUCATION

Web & Software Development Student

The Iron Yard Greenville Summer 2017

B.S. Psychology Based Human Relations

Connecticut College 2008 - 2012

Magna Cum Laude; Phi Beta Kappa; Dean's High Honors